A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Tobacco and Flour Inspector Records, 1776-1878
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Tobacco Inspector returns, 1776-1878 (APA 296)., Extent: 23 boxes (10.35 cu. ft.). (Box 1-23)
  - Stuart's Creek Warehouse (Nelson County), 1790-1791. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Suffolk Warehouse (Nansemond County), 1786-1799, 1802-1804. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Swann's Creek Warehouse (Amherst County), 1789-1801. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Swann's Creek Warehouse (Amherst County), 1801-1816. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Tappahannock Warehouse (Essex County), 1821-1832. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Totusky Warehouse (Richmond County), 1782-1788. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Totusky Warehouse (Richmond County), 1788-1794. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Totusky Warehouse (Richmond County), 1794-1803. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Town's Warehouse (Prince Edward County), 1799-1810, 1817-1823. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Trent's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1791-1801. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Trent's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1801-. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Trent's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1808-1817. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Trent's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1817-1822. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Tye River Warehouse (Nelson County), 1793-1808. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Tye River Warehouse (Nelson County), 1808-1824. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Tye River Warehouse (Nelson County), 1824-1834. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Tye River Warehouse (Nelson County), 1834-1848. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Tye River Warehouse (Nelson County), 17. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Union Warehouse (Botetourt County), 1823-1825, 1835-1838. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Urbanna Warehouse (Middlesex County), 1780-1783, 1786-1791. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Urbanna Warehouse (Middlesex County), 1791-1810. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Veneble's Warehouse (Mecklenburg County), 1838-1848, 1850-1863. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Ware Warehouse (Gloucester County), 1801-1802. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Warwick Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1777-1778, 1781-1788. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Westbrook Warehouse (Dinwiddie County), 1792-1805. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Westbrook Warehouse (Dinwiddie County), 1805-1816. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Westbrook Warehouse (Dinwiddie County), 1816-1824. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Peterburg), 1791-1802. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Petersburg), 1802-1814. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Petersburg), 1814-1828. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Petersburg), 1828-1839. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Petersburg), 1839-1843. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Petersburg), 1843-1852. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Petersburg), 1852-1856. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Petersburg), 1856-1859. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Petersburg), 1859-1860. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - West Hill Warehouse (Petersburg), 1860-1863. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Wicomico Warehouse (Northumberland County), 1781-1788. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Wicomico Warehouse (Northumberland County), 1788-1802. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Wicomico Warehouse (Northumberland County), 1802-1817. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Williams and Piping Tree Warehouse (King William County), 1777-1778, 1780-1781. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Wimbush's Warehouse (Halifax County), 1817-1824. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Woodson's Warehouse (Cumberland County), 1791-1799. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Woodson's Warehouse (Cumberland County), 1799-1811. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Woodson's Warehouse (Cumberland County), 1811-1824. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Yeocomico and Kinsale Warehouse (Westmoreland County), 1780-1798. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - York Warehouse (York County), 1783-1792. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - York Warehouse (York County), 1792-1805. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified, n.d.. (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Series II: Flour Inspector returns, 1794-1858 (APA 296)., Extent: 1 box (.45 cu. ft.). (Box 24)
  Flour Inspector returns, 1794-1858, are housed in 1 box, and are arranged alphabetically by locality. These returns consist of accounts with the Commonwealth for expenses incurred for salaries, supplies, and services, and include amounts of fines collected for deficiencies in flour weight.
  Alphabetically by locality.
  - Alexandria, 1794, 1796-1800. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Fredericksburg, 1806-1807, 1824-1825, 1828-1846, 1852. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lynchburg, 1805, 1809, 1847-1848. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Petersburg, 1819-1822, 1824, 1827, 1829-1831, 1839-1840, 1842-1849. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Richmond, 1798-1809. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Richmond, 1809-1833. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Richmond, 1834-1849, 1857-1858. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Scottsville, 1833, 1842, 1847. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Winchester, 1837-1839, 1844-1846, 1848-1849. (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Series III: Tobacco Manifests, 1789-1791; 1804-1809 (APA 296)., Extent: 2 boxes (.9 cu. ft.). (Box 25-26)
  Tobacco Manifests, 1806-1809, are housed in 2 boxes, and are arranged chronologically. These manifests document ship cargo and include the amount of tobacco on board, name of the ship and master, home port, and where bound in the header of each document. Manifests include colums for mark, number, tare weight, net weight, name of warehouse, and by whom shipped. Each manifest is certified by the master of the ship.
  Chronologically.
  - Tobacco manifests, 1789-1791, undated. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1804 Oct-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1805 Mar. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1805 Apr. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1805 May. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1805 June. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1805 July. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1805 Aug. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1805 Oct-Nov. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1805 Dec. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1806 Jan-Feb. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1806 Mar-Apr. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1806 May. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1806 June. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1806 July. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1806 Aug-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1806 Oct. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1806 Nov-Dec. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1807 Jan-Mar. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1807 Apr-May. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1807 June. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1807 July. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1807 Aug. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1807 Sept. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1807 Oct-Nov. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Tobacco manifests, 1807 Dec. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Tobacco manifests (No. 1-7), 1808 Jan-May. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Tobacco manifests (No. 8-15), 1808 June-Aug. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Tobacco manifests (No. 16-24), 1808 Sept-Nov. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Tobacco manifests (No. 25-28), 1808 Dec-1809 Jan. (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Series IV: Burned Tobacco Claims, 1776-1858 (APA 296)., Extent: 2 boxes (.9 cu. ft.). (Box 27-28)
  Burned Tobacco Claims, 1776-1858, are housed in 2 boxes, and are arranged chronologically. Claims include lists, vouchers and receipts for tobacco burned at Byrd's Warehouse, Dixon's Warehouse, Rocky Ridge Warehouse, Robert Bolling's Warehouse, Royston's Warehouse, Nicholas' Warehouse and Shockoe Warehouse. Vouchers include date, name of claimant, amount of claim, name of warehouse, and commissioner's authorization for a warrant to be issued. Receipts include name of warehouse, date, type and amount of tobacco burned, and the name of the claimant.
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1776, 1780-1781, 1798. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Byrd's Warehouse], 1788 Apr-May. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Byrd's Warehouse], 1788 June-Dec. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Byrd's Warehouse], 1789 Feb-May. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Byrd's Warehouse], 1789 June. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Byrd's Warehouse], 1789 July-Dec. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Rocky Ridge Warehouse], 1790-1794. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Rocky Ridge Warehouse], 1795-1796. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Dixon's Warehouse], 1797 Feb-Mar. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Dixon's Warehouse], 1797 Apr-Aug. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Dixon's Warehouse], 1798-1799. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1799 Jan-Feb. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1799 Mar-Apr. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1800. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1800 May-July. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1800 Sept. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1800 Nov. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1800 Oct. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1800 Dec. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Robert Bolling's Warehouse], 1801. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Royston's Warehouse], 1807-1808. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Royston's Warehouse], 1808 May-June. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Royston's Warehouse], 1808 July-Aug. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Royston's Warehouse], 1808 Sept-Dec. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Royston's Warehouse], 1810 June-Aug. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Nicholas' Warehouse], 1810 Sept-Dec. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Nicholas' Warehouse], 1811 Jan-Feb. (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Shockoe Warehouse], 1848-1849. (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Shockoe Warehouse], 1856 Mar. (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Burned Tobacco Claims [Shockoe Warehouse], 1856 Apr-Aug, 1858. (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Series V: Correspondence and loose records, 1777-1866 (APA 296)., Extent: 1 box (.45 cu. ft.). (Box 29)
  Correspondence and loose records, 1777-1866, are housed in 1 box, and are arranged alphabetically. Includes Auditor's correspondence with inspectors, commissioners, legislators and the Governor's Office, Superintendent of Public Warehouse returns, as well accounts, appointments, lists, notes, opinions, and resolutions.
  - Accounts for rents, 1790-1791, 1793, 1795, 1797. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Appointments of tobacco inspectors since the war, 1865-1866. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Certificates of inspection of merchantable tobacco (Morton's Warehouse), 1777-1778. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Charlotte County tax, 1781-1783. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence of the Auditor of Public Accounts, 1792-1864. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Grand jury tobacco price estimates, 1780-1785. (Box 29, Folder 5a)
  - House of Delegates resolutions, 1786, 1788. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Judgment (Meriwether's Warehouse), 1787. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - List of returns received at the Auditor's Office, 1865. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - List of tobacco exported, 1792-1794. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - List of tobacco sold after two years, 1787-1800. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Lists of warehouse accounts, 1843-1864. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Notes, 1760-1865. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Opinion of the Attorney General, 1855. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Senate resolution, 1861. (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Superintendent of Public Warehouse (Petersburg), 1814-1822. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Superintendent of Public Warehouse (Petersburg), 1822-1842. (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Superintendent of Public Warehouse (Richmond), 1825-1829, 1832-1850. (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Superintendent of Public Warehouse (Richmond), 1858, 1860, 1864. (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Series VI: Tobacco Inspectors book, 1781-1782 (APA 297)., Extent: 1 volume. (Box 30)
  Tobacco Inspectors book, 1781-1782, consists of one volume that is arranged by warehouse name (though names are not in alphabetical order). Each warehouse entry includes name and location of the warehouse, date tobacco received, names and marks of planters delivering hogsheads of tobacco to the warehouse, quantity of tobacco by weight (gross, tare, nett), and disposition.
- Series VII: Ledger of accounts with tobacco inspectors, 1781 Nov-1789 Dec (APA 298)., Extent: 1 volume. (Box 30)
  Ledger of accounts with tobacco inspectors, 1781 Nov-1789 Dec, consists of one volume that is arranged alphabetically by warehouse name. Volume contains accounts with inspectors of tobacco for duties assessed and collected. Index in the front of the volume.
- Series VIII: Tobacco Duty Affidavits for refund or surplus, 1787-1790 (APA 299)., Extent: 1.15 cubic feet. (Box 1-3)
  Tobacco Duty Affidavits for refund or surplus, 1787-1790, are housed in 3 boxes, and are arranged chronologically. Affidavits certify the name of the claimant, name of the warehouse, number of hogsheads of tobacco, dates and amount of duty paid, and include signatures of sworn witnesses and officials. May also include receipts in lieu of affidavits that include name, warehouse, date, type of tobacco and weight.
  During its session begun in May 1784 the General Assembly passed an act entitled "An Act to Appoint Commissioners to Settle Losses Sustained by the Burning of the Warehouses at Rocky Ridge," in Chesterfield County, near Richmond. To cover the losses, an additional duty of three shillings per hogshead of tobacco was levied effective 1 October 1784. In 1786 the General Assembly authorized an additional duty of six shillings per hogshead of tobacco beginning 10 January 1787. The duties were collected by the tobacco inspectors.
  In 1787 the General Assembly, noting that the additional six shillings tax on tobacco had in many cases been paid before 10 January 1787, ordered this money refunded. Upon receipt of an affidavit or other satisfactory proof, the auditor of public accounts issued the claimant a warrant for the full amount of the tax he had paid.
  - Affidavits, 1787. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Apr 8-11. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Apr 15-19. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Apr 22-29. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Affidavits, 1788 May 2-5. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Affidavits, 1788 May 7-9. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Affidavits, 1788 May 10-19. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Affidavits, 1788 May 20-29. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Affidavits, 1788 June 3-5. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Affidavits, 1788 June 9-14. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Affidavits, 1788 June 16-30. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Affidavits, 1788 July. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Aug 1-20. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Aug 23-29. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Sept 1-5. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Sept 8-10. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Sept 11-16. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Sept 18-30. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Oct 4-11. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Oct 13-31. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Nov 1-11. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Nov 12-26. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Affidavits, 1788 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Affidavits, 1789 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Affidavits, 1789 Feb-Mar. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Affidavits, 1789 Apr-May. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Affidavits, 1789 June-Aug. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Affidavits, 1789 Sept-Nov. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Affidavits, 1790 Jan-May. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Affidavits, 1790 June-Nov. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Affidavits, 1790 June-Nov. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Series IX: Public Tobacco Warehouse vouchers, 1776-1865 (APA 293)., Extent: XX cubic feet. (Box XX-XX)
  Public Tobacco Warehouse vouchers, 1776-1865, are housed in XX boxes. This series includes Tobacco receipts, 1776-1787; a List of inspectors, 1783-1820; and Vouchers, 1781, 1785-1793, 1897-1865.
  Tobacco receipts, 1776-1787, include name, date, name of warehouse, type and weight of tobacco. Includes receipts for the following warehouses: Aquia, John Bolling's, Robert Bolling's, Bollingbrook, Blandford, Boyd's, Boyd's Hole, Brickhouse, Byrd's, Cedarpoint, Crutchfield, Davis', Falls, Falmouth, Fredericksburg, Gibson's, Merriwether's, Nominy, Noble's, Osborne's, Page's, Rocky Ridge, Royston's, Shockoe, and Yeomico.
  List of tobacco inspectors, 1783-1820, includes name of warehouse, date of bond, and name of inspector.
  During its session begun in October 1776 the General Assembly passed an act concerning the revival of public tobacco warehouses. Tobacco inspectors, who examined and graded tobacco at public warehouses, were selected by county courts and appointed by the governor. In 1778 the General Assembly directed inspectors to certify charges for repairing or contructing new buildings to the treasurer for payment.
  During its session begun in May 1782 the General Assemlby passed another act for the maintenance of public warehouses. If the owner of a public warehouse refused to make needed repairs, then bids were taken and the work was done by contractors who were paid by the inspectors. On 26 December 1796 the General Assembly passed an act that authorized county courts to appoint commissioners to supervise the tobacco inspectors and see to it that the warehouses were maintained and that the weights and scales were kept in working order. The county courts certified the commissioners' accounts to the auditor of public accounts.
  - Tobacco receipts, 1776-1779. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Tobacco receipts, 1779 Jan 31. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Tobacco receipts (A-C), 1780. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tobacco receipts (D-Y), 1780. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tobacco receipts (B-D), 1781. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tobacco receipts (F-R), 1781. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tobacco receipts (Royston's Warehouse), 1781. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Tobacco receipts, 1782. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Tobacco receipts, 1786 Oct 11. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Tobacco receipts, 1787 Nov 6. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Tobacco receipts (fragments), undated. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - List of tobacco inspectors, 1783-1820. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Catpoint Warehouse), 1781 Jan 27. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (House of Delegates Resolution - Leed's Warehouse), 1781 Jan 29. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Accomack County), 1781 Feb 14. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Pitt's, Guildford and Pungoteague Warehouses), 1781 Feb 15. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1781 Feb 22. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Machotack Warehouse), 1781 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County), 1781 Mar 12. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Spotsylvania County), 1781 Mar 13. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1781 Oct 6. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Stafford County), 1781 Oct 19. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Page's Warehouse), 1782 Oct 1. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1781 Oct 3. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1782 Oct 9. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Invoice), 1782 Nov 26. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1782 Dec 9. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Page's Warehouse), 1783 May 9. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1783 June 24. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1783 Oct 2. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1783 Oct 28. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Littlepage's Warehouse), 1783 Nov 6. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Brickhouse Warehouse), 1783 Dec 6. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Aquia Warehouse), 1784 Feb 24. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Littlepage's Warehouse), 1784 Mar 16. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Rocket's Warehouse), 1784 Apr 15. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Lowpoint), 1784 Apr 16. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Mattox Warehouse), 1784 Apr 17. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse - flour and hemp), 1784 May 10. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1784 May 12. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Cabinpoint Warehouse), 1784 May 15. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Cottage Landing Warehouse), 1784 June 17. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1784 July 12. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1784 July 12. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Littlepage's Warehouse), 1784 July 30. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1784 Aug 16. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1784 Sept 15. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Pitt's Warehouse), 1784 Oct 7. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Pungoteague Warehouse), 1784 Oct 7. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1784 Oct 7. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Bowler's Warehouse), 1784 Oct 15. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1784 Oct 16. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1784 Oct 19. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Indian Warehouse - Northumberland County), 1784 Oct 22. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1784 Oct 22. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1784 Oct 22. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Totusky Warehouse), 1784 Oct 23. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Bowler's Warehouse), 1784 Oct 25. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1784 Nov 3. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 17. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Cottage Landing Warehouse), 1784 Nov 10. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Page's Warehouse), 1784 Nov 30. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Pocomoke Warehouse - Accomack County), 1784 Dec 1. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Beckwith's Warehouse), 1784 Dec 18. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Aquia Warehouse), 1784 Dec 20. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1785 Feb 11. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Bowler's Warehouse), 1785 Feb 25. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1785 Apr 22. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1785 May 1. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1785 May 23. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Aquia Warehouse), 1785 May 26. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Littlepage's Warehouse), 1785 May 27. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1785 June 14. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Page's Warehouse), 1785. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1785 July 21. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1785 Aug 16. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Hobb's Hole Warehouse), 1785 Aug 19. (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1785 Sept 13. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1785 Sept 26. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Littlepage's Warehouse), 1785 Oct 4. (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1785 Oct 7. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1785 Oct 7. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1785 Oct 7. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1785 Oct 14. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1785 Oct 14. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1785 Oct 15. (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1785 Oct 17. (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Alexandria Warehouse), 1785 Oct 18. (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Dymer's Warehouse - Lancaster County), 1785 Oct 19. (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Vouchers (Leeds and Mattox Warehouse), 1785 Oct 19. (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1785 Oct 20. (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1785 Oct 25. (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Vouchers (Smithfield and Fulgham's Warehouse), 1785 Oct 27. (Box 2, Folder 71)